const quizQuestions = [{
        question: "Who promised that they would never lose another fight until they defeated a certain someone?",
        choices: ["Luffy", "Sanji", "Zoro", "Usopp"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How did Luffy get the scar under his eye?",
        choices: ["Atacked by bandits", "Fight with animals", "Himself", "Fight with another villager"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the first member of the SH crew to try and recruit a new member besides Luffy?",
        choices: ["Nami", "Sanji", "Zoro", "Usopp"],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What made Crocodile join Luffy's 'Rescue Ace Crew'?",
        choices: ["Luffy", "Jinbei", "Ace", "Ivancov"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the first marine Admiral to be shown in the series?",
        choices: ["Akainu", "Kizaru", "Aokiji", "Sengoku"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Who gave Shanks the scar on his eye?",
        choices: ["Dragon", "Marshall D", "Akainu", "Himself"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many crewmates did Luffy say he wanted at the beginning of the series?",
        choices: ["9", "13", "10", "15"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Who said- Zoro should cut diamond next?",
        choices: ["Luffy", "Mihawk", "Kuina", "Daz Bones"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the first recruit of the SH crew?",
        choices: ["Nami", "Sanji", "Zoro", "Usopp"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many confirmed D clan members are there?",
        choices: ["8", "14", "11", "18"],
        answer: 1
    },
];

function startGame() {

}

function restartGame() {

}

function displayScore() {

}

function showQuestion() {

}

function showChoices() {

}

function checkAnswer() {

}

function finishQuiz() {

}